{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "That is the girl ________ I want to marry.",
      "a": "whose",
      "b": "who",
      "c": "which",
      "d": "whom",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to) \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n- We prefer which when the number of choices is limited ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Carol's father, ________ is 60, goes running every day.",
      "a": "whom",
      "b": "which",
      "c": "whose",
      "d": "who",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to) \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n- We prefer which when the number of choices is limited ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The wedding, to ________ very few people were invited, took place yesterday.",
      "a": "which",
      "b": "who",
      "c": "whom",
      "d": "that",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n- We prefer which when the number of choices is limited \n- That normally refers to things but it may refer to a class or type of person.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "________ car is that?' 'My father's.'",
      "a": "Who",
      "b": "Whose",
      "c": "Which",
      "d": "Whom",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action)\n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action)\n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to)\n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them\n+We prefer which when the number of choices is limited",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The Games,________ lasted two weeks, are over now.",
      "a": "which",
      "b": "who",
      "c": "whose",
      "d": "whom",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action)\n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action)\n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to)\n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them\n+We prefer which when the number of choices is limited",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is the book in ________ she is interested.",
      "a": "which",
      "b": "whom",
      "c": "that",
      "d": "whose",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n- We prefer which when the number of choices is limited \n- That normally refers to things but it may refer to a class or type of person.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mary,________ mother is an opera singer, is learning music.",
      "a": "which",
      "b": "whose",
      "c": "that",
      "d": "whom",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- We use whose + noun as the subject of the relative clause",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "These are the grammar books in ________ I am interested.",
      "a": "which",
      "b": "who",
      "c": "whom",
      "d": "that",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n+We prefer which when the number of choices is limited \n- That normally refers to things but it may refer to a class or type of person.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The lady ________ you talked on the phone is coming immediately.",
      "a": "which",
      "b": "to whom",
      "c": "whom",
      "d": "who",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- That normally refers to things but it may refer to a class or type of person. \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n+We prefer which when the number of choices is limited",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Terry, ________ you met yesterday, is going to get married today.",
      "a": "which",
      "b": "who",
      "c": "that",
      "d": "whom",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n+We prefer which when the number of choices is limited \n- That normally refers to things but it may refer to a class or type of person.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}